[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64b9819b4e2c611bba93c1be"
  },
  "question": "Who was the first President of India?",
  "options": [
    "Dr. APJ Abdul Kalam",
    "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "Dr. Rajendra Prasad",
    "Jawaharlal Nehru"
  ],
  "answer": "Dr. Rajendra Prasad",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64b982e41078fb49cf4293e5"
  },
  "question": "Who was the first Prime Minister of India?",
  "options": [
    "Jawaharlal Nehru",
    "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "Sir Syed Ahmad Khan",
    "Dr. Rajendra Prasad"
  ],
  "answer": "Jawaharlal Nehru",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64b983401078fb49cf4293e8"
  },
  "question": "How many Cricket world cups does India have?",
  "options": [
    "One",
    "Two",
    "Three",
    "Four"
  ],
  "answer": "Two",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf40216f3633c80a84b23"
  },
  "question": "Name of the first university of India?",
  "options": [
    "Nalanda University",
    "Taxshila University",
    "Jawahar University",
    "Dronacharya University"
  ],
  "answer": "Nalanda University",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf41716f3633c80a84b26"
  },
  "question": "Which Indian state has the least literacy rate?",
  "options": [
    "Bihar",
    "Rajasthan",
    "Arunachal Pradesh",
    "Orissa"
  ],
  "answer": "Bihar",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf42416f3633c80a84b29"
  },
  "question": "Name of the first deputy Prime Minister of India?",
  "options": [
    "R.N. Shukla",
    "V.R. Gill",
    "Sardar Vallabh Bhai Patel",
    "D.B. Mahawar"
  ],
  "answer": "Sardar Vallabh Bhai Patel",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf42f16f3633c80a84b2c"
  },
  "question": "Name of first Space Tourist of India?",
  "options": [
    "DP Mahadevan",
    "Santosh George",
    "Niel Arm Strong",
    "V.R. Gill"
  ],
  "answer": "Santosh George",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf43a16f3633c80a84b2f"
  },
  "question": "Name of the First Indian Prime Minister who resigned from Office?",
  "options": [
    "Indira Gandhi",
    "Moraji Desai",
    "Jawahar Lal Nehru",
    "Rajiv Gandhi"
  ],
  "answer": "Moraji Desai",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf44b16f3633c80a84b33"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is the capital of Arunachal Pradesh?",
  "options": [
    "Itanagar",
    "Dispur",
    "Imphal",
    "Panaji"
  ],
  "answer": "Itanagar",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf45816f3633c80a84b36"
  },
  "question": "What is the state flower of Haryana?",
  "options": [
    "Rhododendron",
    "Lotus",
    "Golden Shower",
    "Not Declared"
  ],
  "answer": "Lotus",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf46116f3633c80a84b39"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following states is not located in the North?",
  "options": [
    "Himachal Pradesh",
    "Jammu and Kashmir",
    "Haryana",
    "Jharkhand"
  ],
  "answer": "Jharkhand",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf59221faf1cb242ae327"
  },
  "question": "In which of the following state, the main language is Khasi?",
  "options": [
    "Mizoram",
    "Nagaland",
    "Meghalaya",
    "Tripura"
  ],
  "answer": "Meghalaya",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "64bbf59f21faf1cb242ae32a"
  },
  "question": "Which is the largest coffee-producing state of India?",
  "options": [
    "Kerala",
    "Karnataka",
    "Arunachal Pradesh",
    "Tamil Nadu"
  ],
  "answer": "Karnataka",
  "__v": 0
}]